<resources>
    <!-- App name -->
    <string name="app_name">MyKampus</string>

    <!-- Navigation headers -->
    <string name="nav_header_email">contact@kamtjatka.dk</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <!-- Menu actions -->
    <string name="action_signin">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_signout">Sign out</string>
    <string name="action_upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="action_web">Website</string>

    <!-- Side Menu actions -->
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_flats">Flats</string>
    <string name="menu_common_rooms">Common Rooms</string>
    <string name="menu_faq">Faq</string>

    <!-- Notifications strings -->
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name">Kamtjatka Notifications</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribe_failed">Failed to subscribe to channel</string>
    <string name="fcm_message">New Message</string>
    <string name="quickstart_message">You are subscribed to Kamtjatka notifications</string>
    <string name="log_token">Log Token</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribed">Subscribed to weather topic</string>
    <string name="msg_token_fmt">FCM registration Token: %s</string>
    <string name="menu_feedbacks">Feedbacks</string>

    <!-- Guides strings -->
    <string name="welcome">Do you have any questions about the Danish way of life? Would you like to know more
places to socialize in Horsens? Or do you want to make a career for yourself at one of the
many interesting companies in the Horsens area? Our welcome guide is your helping hand
when settling in Horsens. Please contact BusinessHorsens to learn more.
BusinessHorsens can also arrange for you to talk to one of our welcome ambassadors –
a group of knowledgeable and friendly volunteer international citizens who are eager to
answer any practical questions you might have about settling and living in Horsens.
BusinessHorsens
Vitus Bering Innovation Park
Chr. M. Østergaards Vej 4a
DK-8700 Horsens
Phone: +45 7561 1888
E-mail: mail@businesshorsens.dk
Opening hours: Monday - Thursday: 8.00 am - 3.00 pm and Friday 8.00 am - 2.00 pm</string>

    <string name="arriving">To make sure that you have all the right papers and registrations you need in order to be able
to work and live in Denmark, we have collected some information for you about the official
matters to take care of when moving to Denmark.
International Citizen Service – all the services you need in one place
The International Citizen Service (ICS) makes dealing with Danish authorities as easy as pos-
sible – for you, your partner, and for Danish companies that employ foreign workers.
You will find an International Citizen Service office in each of the four largest cities in Den-
mark: Copenhagen, Aarhus, Odense and Aalborg. The Municipality of Horsens works with ICS
Aarhus to ensure that you get off to a good start in Denmark and Horsens.
All the public authorities you typically need to deal with are represented at ICS Aarhus. In most
cases, you will only need to talk to your ICS office to take care of your paperwork and find
answers to your questions.</string>

    <string name="cleaning">It is always the responsibility of the tenants to keep the apartment clean and tidy.For health reasons, but
also to prevent damage to the buildings, apartments should be cleaned on a weekly basis. Bathrooms and
kitchen twice a week
No garbage bags on the floors, throw them out or have them in bins.
Clean up after you when you have been using the common rooms.</string>

    <string name="room_inspection">During the first 5 days after your tenancy begins, we will be conducting an inspection of your room.
You will receive an invitation, but you are not required to be present.
After the inspection you will receive an inspection report about the state of your room. If you do
not agree with the inspection, or if you encounter defects not mentioned, you must notify us in
writing within 2 weeks after the tenancy beginning date. Report to contract@kamtjatka.dk
Also please count the inventory on the inventory list you have received, and return the list 2 weeks
after the tenancy beginning date. This way you will not be held liable for damages or shortcomings.</string>

    <string name="maintenance">For safety and documentation purposes, email must be used for maintenance requests. Send a
detailed description of the problem to contract@kamtjatka.dk
We will tent to problems as fast as possible. For issues in common areas we will gain access to the
apartment and leave a note. If maintenance is required in your private room, you must be home or
give explicit consent to our staff entering the room without you present. </string>

    <string name="keys">Broken keys can be replaced at the office. You will be charged for the replacement key, currently
dkk 250,00. If the key is broken inside the lock, a locksmith will be called and you will be charged
the related cost.
If you lose a key, we will need to recode the locks. You will be charged the related cost, currently
dkk 1.850,00.
For calls outside of normal working hours regarding lost or broken keys, you will be charged a
service fee of dkk 400,00.</string>

    <string name="check_out">When your contract is coming to an end, you will receive information from us on email regarding
the checkout.
When planning your trip back home please note that checkout is only done on weekdays and only
in normal business hours. Please schedule travel accordingly. </string>

    <string name="bikes">Parking of bicycles are only allowed in designated areas or storage rooms. Bicycles are not allowed
inside the apartments. All bicycles must be sticker with your room number. This sticker can be
collected at the office. </string>

    <string name="smoking">Drosselbo has a non-smoking policy inside all buildings, the policy includes tenants as well as
visitors. Any tenant violating the nonsmoking policy will be liable to pay damages including a total
repaint of discolored walls.</string>

</resources>